Boys will be boys. . . some longer than others.
Grown Ups is a comedy film directed by Dennis Dugan.
After their high school basketball coach passes away, five good friends and
former teammates reunite for a Fourth of July holiday weekend.
Lenny Feder, played by Adam Sandler.
Eric Lamonsoff, played by Kevin James.
Kurt McKenzie, played by Chris Rock.
Marcus Higgins, played by David Spade.
Rob Hilliard, played by Rob Schneider.
Roxanne Chase-Feder, played by Salma Hayek Pinault.
Grown Ups is a 2010 American comedy film directed by Dennis Dugan, written by Adam Sandler and Fred Wolf, produced by Sandler and Jack Giarraputo, and
starring Sandler, Kevin James, Chris Rock, David Spade, and Rob Schneider, with Salma Hayek, Maria Bello, and Maya Rudolph in supporting roles.
The film's plot tells the story of five lifelong friends who won their
junior high school basketball championship in 1978.
They reunite three decades later for a 4th of July weekend after
learning about the death of their former coach.
Produced by Sandler's Happy Madison Productions in collaboration with Relativity Media, Grown
Ups was released in the United States on June 25, 2010, by Columbia Pictures.
Despite receiving negative reviews from critics, it grossed $272.2
million and led to a sequel, Grown Ups 2, in 2013.
The film explores themes of friendship, overweight,
affectation, convertible, swing.
The tone is lighthearted.